(Howard:)-Hey, guys.
-Happy Thanksgiving.
(Sheldon:)It smells wonderful.
(Sheldon:)Is anyone slaving away
in the kitchen?
(Sheldon:)-Because I, too, know--
-Sheldon.
(Penny:)Here. Thank you for having us.
(Howard:)What's with you?
(Leonard:)She's mad at me
(Leonard:)because she just found out
she's married to Zack.
(Howard:)Really?
That dumb-ass you used to date?
(Howard:)That's hysterical.
(Penny:)I can't believe I felt bad
for opening this in the car.
(Amy:)You need any help?
Yeah, can you reach
that gravy boat up there?
(Amy:)-Uh, sure.
-Great.
(Raj:)That makes one of you.
(Raj:)Okay we have a lot to do
and not much time to do it.
Bernadette, you're on com,
gravy and yam detail.
(Raj:)Amy, you're on rolls, cranberries
(Raj:)and making sure Bernadette stays
away from the marshmallows.
(Raj:)That's right, I see you.
(Raj:)Okay if you have
any questions,